[EXAMINER] Please describe a place
that you sometimes visit
which is very important to you.
You should say where it is, and
how often and why you go there.
[WOMAN]
One place that is very important in
my life is my grandmother's house.
She lives in a small village
in the south of the country.
I go there every summer, and any time
when I can get away for a few days.
I go there to visit my grandmother,
get away from the city and relax.
The village is just a group of
white houses on a hillside
and a couple of shops,
and it's really peaceful.
There's no traffic,
just the sound of goat bells,
birds and insects.
One reason why I like it is
because it's a beautiful place.
My grandmother has a lovely garden
and we always sit outside in
the shade of her olive trees,
drinking sweet tea and chatting.
It's so peaceful.
But the main reason why this place is so
important to me is
because of my grandmother.
She is so kind to me, and
wonderful to talk to.
Whenever I have a problem in my life,
she has good advice for me.
Also, she is a great cook
and the meals she prepares are
simple but so fresh and...
rich? Er no, er...
no, I mean tasty.
And she's always giving me eh...
What do you call them?
- small plates of food during the day,
so I always return home feeling
calm and refreshed - and fat!
I wouldn't like to live there, though.
I prefer living in the city,
definitely. I'm a city person.
I couldn't live in a small
village where everybody knows
each other and nothing happens.
I'd rather live in a busy,
exciting place.
But I really love visiting
the village for the holidays.