[LIU] Well, in my opinion, the best thing
about cycling is the exercise.
You can go from A to B and
keep fit at the same time.
What do you think?
[VIKI] I agree.
And it's quiet and clean.
I mean, bikes don't create pollution
like cars, and they don't use oil.
[LIU] Hmm, yes, bikes are
better for the environment.
[VIKI] Yes, exactly. But on the other hand,
there are bad points too. I mean,
it can be quite dangerous, can't it?
[LIU] Yes, that's true. Especially in
the city with all the traffic.
An another bad point is the weather -
cycling isn't pleasant in
rainy and cold conditions.
[VIKI] Uh, uh.
No. And it can be really
tiring if you go up a hill.
I don't cycle because I live in the
mountains, and all the
roads are really steep.
If I lived in a flat place like Holland,
I might cycle more.
What about you? Do you cycle?
[LIU] Sometimes, but only on holidays,
not to go to work.
I think the people in the
photos are going to work.
[VIKI] So, which place do you think looks
more dangerous for the cyclists?
[LIU] Well, I would say it's
OK in the first picture,
because there is a special part
of the road for the cyclist,
but not in the second picture -
the cyclists are in the middle of the
traffic, and it looks quite dangerous.
[VIKI] Yes, and I think the man in the
first picture is better prepared.
He's wearing a bright colored coat
and - what do you call it?
A cycling hat?
[LIU] A helmet, you mean?
[VIKI] Helmet, exactly. The people in the
second picture haven't got helmets.
[LIU] Hmm.
[VIKI] But there again,
it could be more dangerous
in the first picture,
because the traffic is going much faster,
isn't it?
[LIU] Hmm, yes, I suppose so.
But there is plenty of space.
Hmm, on the whole,
I think it's more dangerous
in the second picture.
[VIKI] Yeah.
Yeah, I think you're
probably right.