OK, so we have to choose one picture
to put on the front of the brochure.
Shall we get started, then?
Er, let's see...
It's really difficult.
Personally, if I were choosing a holiday,
I think I would pick up a brochure with
a picture of the dancers on the front,
but that's because I enjoy folk dancing.
Maybe that would not be so
good for most people.
No, possibly not. To be honest,
that one looks boring.
If you ask me, we should choose one
which most people would find attractive.
How about the photo of the food?
Everybody likes eating!
That's true, but I don't think
Scotland is famous for food.
I think if people wanted a food holiday,
they would choose Italy or
France or somewhere like that.
OK, that's a good point.
It's the same with the picture of the beach -
it's beautiful,
but I've never heard of people going
to Scotland for a beach holiday.
From what I've heard,
it's always raining in Britain.
Yes, that's right,
everybody says that the weather's terrible there.
Well, ...we could use the picture
of the mountain climbers.
It would give people the idea of
things you can do in Scotland.
What that would be very popular? I doubt it.
Maybe we should focus on history and culture.
What's happening in the first picture,
for example? I've no idea.
It looks like a carnival or something.
But I think I would opt for the castle.
To me, that's a typical image of Scotland,
and I can imagine it would look
great on the cover of the brochure.
What do you think?
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
the carnival or the castle would be fine.
So, shall we use the castle then?
Yes, OK. That's fine by me.
Right, so I think we're agreed.
We'll use the photo of the castle.