Please describe this photograph.
What do you think is happening
and what is your opinion about it?
This picture shows two young men
chatting on a park bench.
They are wearing casual clothes
and training shoes.
One of them has glasses.
It is a cloudy day.
In the background,
we can see trees and grass.
There are a lot of red and orange
leaves on the ground,
so I would say it's autumn in a cold country,
perhaps in the north of Europe,
or maybe in North America.
There is a pram to the left of the bench
and another one to the right.
I would guess that they're babies in the prams,
although we can't actually see them.
And I suppose that the
young men are the fathers.
The picture is slightly unusual,
because we normally expect to see
mothers looking after babies.
In most parts of the world,
childcare is traditionally the mother's job.
But I think the idea for this photo is good,
and because in my opinion,
both parents should have equal
responsibility for the children.
The picture
also makes us think about another question.
It is the middle of the day.
Why aren't the men at work?
It could be the weekend, of course,
or perhaps a public holiday.
But there is another possibility.
Perhaps the men look after their
homes and the children full time,
and their wives go to work.
We normally talk about housewives,
but in this case maybe they are house husbands.
I know this is unusual,
but why not?
I love that idea.