Hello, I'm Martin.
What's your name please?
I'm Cristina. And where are you
from, Cristina? I'm from Spain.
Oh, really? Whereabouts in Spain?
From a town called Iznalloz.
It's near the city of Granada.
Oh right. And can you tell me a
little bit about what you do?
Yes, I am a student. I am
studying economics at university.
I also have a part-time
job in a hairdresser's.
And where do you live?
Actually, I live in two places.
During the week, when there are classes,
I live with an aunt in Granada,
near to the university,
and at the weekends I usually go home
to my parents' place in Iznalloz.
But next year I hope to rent a flat
together with a friend of mine.
OK. And how long have you been
studying English. Oh for a long time.
I have been studying English
at school since primary,
and I have also done evening classes
at a language school.
Nowadays, I try to practise by
making friends on social media
and chatting in English.
How important do you think English
will be in your career? Very important.
When I graduate, I hope to apply for a job
in a multinational company.
I want to work abroad,
in Britain or maybe another country,
you know.
I would really love to see new places,
meet new people, see the world.
I've never been outside Spain before,
it's too expensive,
But I've always wanted to travel.