Good morning, Mr Mason.
Take a seat, please. Thank you.
Now, I can see from your CV
that you graduated from Bristol
University just over a year ago.
Yes, that's right.
So, can you tell me a little bit
about what you've been doing since then?
Yes, first of all,
I got a summer job as a group leader
at a children's summer camp in Canada.
That's something that I'd
previously done in France,
and I've always enjoyed working with kids.
When that was over,
I came back to London and got
a job as a studio assistant in
a local community TV station.
What were your duties there?
Well, basically I did everything, you know,
from taking calls to responding
to emails and maintaining the website,
right the way through to interviewing and
helping out with the filming and editing.
It's a small company so I got a
chance to try a little bit of everything.
What did you enjoy most?
I guess the interviewing. I think I'm
quite outgoing, so I love meeting
people and finding out about them.
I see, right. So what about the future?
Where do you see yourself in five years' time?
I'd like to work for a larger TV network,
perhaps as an interviewer for
a regular programme,
either interviewing guests in the
studio or going out and about,
interviewing members of the public.
And what made you decide to apply
for a job with us?
I think this is a well-known company
that's got a very good reputation,
so I felt it would be the ideal place
to develop my skills, and hopefully
contribute something with my
enthusiasm and willingness to learn.
OK, well, thank you for coming in today.
Obviously, we have a few more candidates
to consider, so we will be making a
selection in a week or so, and we'll
let you know one way or the other.
OK, thanks.