So I'm here today to present you
with the results of that survey.
Now to do this, I've divided my
presentation into three parts.
Firstly, I'll talk about the
background to the research,
then we'll look at how we
approach the research and thirdly
I'll summarize the key findings
of the research.
So let's start with a brief
description of the background.
So once we selected the 90,000 customers
across your company's three regions,
we then emailed them the survey.
We allowed four weeks for them to
respond to the surveys and after that
period we received a 4% response rate.
Now this is quite good for
this type of survey.
We then analyzed those responses and
compiled them in a report for you.
Let's look at those responses
in a bit more detail.
Now, of that 4%, this blue section
shows that 57% of those
responses came from the region
with the difficulties. That's significant,
as you are more likely to receive
responses from customers who are either
very satisfied or very unsatisfied.
Anyway,
this leads me on to the third and
main part of my presentation:
the actual results of the survey.
Now in front of you,
there's a copy of the survey's findings.
I'm going to summarize the key
findings for each of these questions.
So let's begin with question one,
which asks your customers how likely they
are to recommend your company to a friend.
As you can see, we have used a scale,
with zero being not at all likely
and ten being extremely likely.
According to this chart,
the overall response indicates
that customers are fairly likely
to recommend your company.
However, this chart represents an average
response across the three regions.
If we break these responses down
into the three regions like this,
it illustrates the difference in
customer satisfaction region by region.
Now remember, red and yellow are the regions
with increasing numbers of customers.
Consequently, the responses are quite high,
even as high as ten,
but the lower scores in the
previous chart were caused by the
decline in these blue responses here.
They go down to the
zero level in some cases.